Boy, I used a parser that was already done
and I had to strip it way down. I don't know
if if nobody has told you my story, which was
they they gave me cuz it was my first game,
they gave me nine months to write it and I
finished it in six. Um, and then spent the
next three just cutting stuff out. It was way
way too big to fit because I was the last game
to fit on I think it was a Commodore 64. So, um,
it was all that great stuff that had to be cut.
And so I did a lot of cutting, but I started
with a blackbox um parser. And I don't think
I started with any other game. I mean, I could
be because it was it was a different it it was
just coming at things differently. If I did, it
would have been prism because it was in my mind
it was the most like a mind forever voyaging.
Sorry, which we called prism in development.
Um, but I'm pretty sure I didn't because
that was so huge that I would I would have
spent my first six months just cutting stuff
out of that to make it small enough to build